{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40211cfba6a7877c1377"},"product_asin":"B08HRX87FJ","QAs":[{"question":"Is door alarm available in this model?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What amps socket is needed, 5 or 15amps?","answer":"15 amp is always stable and useful.","votes":"0","username":"Aniket Ghule","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"which year manufactured product will i get if i place the order now ?","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"NEELAM APPLIANCES;","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ice box , ice tray is removable?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"SHRI KRISHNA...,","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40221cfba6a7877c137b"},"product_asin":"B084TH4783","QAs":[{"question":"is there any installation charges?","answer":"No installation charges. Its free. The LG installation engineer will visit your house and gives clear demo on the refrigerator.","votes":"0","username":"Suresh","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do I contact the customer service of lg for repair?","answer":"U can call LG to customer service number. U can find it in Google.","votes":"0","username":"Suresh","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the installation process after delivery? If they take more than 7 days?","answer":"Ideally the installation guy will visit within 24 hrs.","votes":"0","username":"Suresh","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is difference between this fridge and  lg 335l frost-free inverter double door refrigerator (gl-t372jpz3, shiny steel, convertible refrigerator?","answer":"Direct cool refrigerators use less electricity as compared to the frost-free ones. The refrigerators can keep food products fresh. Their exterior part does not heat up as opposed to the frost-free refrigerators.","votes":"0","username":"Mandvi","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you ship it any where in India","answer":"Yes  you can.","votes":"0","username":"Mandvi","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model is this? Does it mean it was manufactured in the model year and been sitting in stock for so long? If so how good will the compressor","answer":"Good enough that you will get 10 years of warranty from the date of purchase..","votes":"0","username":"Karan Verma","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get GST credit on this purchase","answer":"Yes .you can .it's already added in your invoice bill","votes":"0","username":"Mandvi","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it solar Compitable or not?","answer":"it is inverter compatible...it may means it can run on battery capacity ..mean you may supply power through solar as well through inverter battery.. but i am not 100% sure ...kindly research more and share your findings.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Adjustable shelves?","answer":"YES,,, even you can convert freezer section to refrigeration to increase space to put more stuff..","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Froost type","answer":"Running smoothly till now , good product.","votes":"0","username":"Dr Ranadhir Paul","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What mins lenier compressur","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Dr Ranadhir Paul","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"is ice tray movable","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Dr Ranadhir Paul","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40221cfba6a7877c1387"},"product_asin":"B079QP11T3","QAs":[{"question":"क्या gl-b201aspy,aspzebn स्कारलेट प्लुमेरिया 5 star है","answer":"Haa","votes":"0","username":"Manoj","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या स्कारलेट प्लुमेरिया फ्रीज 5 star है","answer":"हाँ है, 4 भी, 5 भी","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many watts is the refrigerator","answer":"90 तो 310 watt","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Market mein yah 13000 mein uplabdh hai","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it need  stabilizer?","answer":"No need","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this frost free ?","answer":"Manual defrost in week 2 times","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या रेट है","answer":"16000 के अंदर","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya mujhe EMI pr refrigerator mil sakta h kya","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"कितने स्टार है इसकी रेटिंग में ?","answer":"4","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is This fridge must need home inverter for run","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Monu gupta","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Under 10000","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Monu gupta","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"I am staying in 2nd floor with no lift facility. Will it be delivered to 2nd floor?","answer":"Chala jayega by courier boys","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"मैं इसे डेबिट कार्ड ईएमआई पर कैसे करेगा","answer":"डेबिट कार्ड से emi पर नही मिलता, use क्रेडिट या ऐमज़ॉन पे लेटर।","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"वह इस प्रोडक्ट को डेबिट कार्ड ईएमआई में कैसे खरीदें","answer":"डेबिट कार्ड से emi नही","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"क्या या डेबिट कार्ड की माई में उपलब्ध है मेरे","answer":"नही","votes":"0","username":"Harsh Pandey","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40231cfba6a7877c1394"},"product_asin":"B09SPZMNHK","QAs":[{"question":"It have lock feature?","answer":"No there is no option of lock, you might need to purchase an external lock facility.","votes":"0","username":"C P.","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is light there inside fridge?","answer":"Light is only present in the below door which is main fridge.","votes":"0","username":"Rahul G.","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which years model it is?","answer":"We got 2022 one","votes":"0","username":"Rahul G.","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40231cfba6a7877c1396"},"product_asin":"B0999S3MD4","QAs":[{"question":"Is there any fridge auto defrost without water collecting tray","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"mohd r.","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the connected power for this Fridge??","answer":"Maybye 198 units per year","votes":"0","username":"mohd r.","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many days door delivery","answer":"3 to 5 days","votes":"0","username":"mohd r.","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whatvis the difference between convertible refrigerator and non convertible refrigerator??","answer":"U can convert your freezer to non freezer","votes":"0","username":"Nishil.SB","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Amazon Gift card are accepted","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"mohd r.","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Convertible refrigerator means?","answer":"Convertible means,you can use the upper unit as a normal refrigerator or as a ice chamber.","votes":"0","username":"Satya Mohapatra","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's Dorcooling are not","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vinodkumar","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year of this product gl-i292rozx (date of question 09/06/2022)","answer":"April 2022","votes":"0","username":"Jaleel ck","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much electricity power is used in 24hrs fridge","answer":"Year-1500k","votes":"0","username":"Pipash das","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year please?? Seems pretty old and that might change the power rating?","answer":"April 2022","votes":"0","username":"Jaleel ck","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is one year warranty??","answer":"One year warranty for ligt weight parts covered under warranty. But no need anything, it is best working refrigerator so far in my case. No Electrical consumption, minimal charges","votes":"0","username":"Dr.T. Alwarsamy ,Ph.D ( Engg .…","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we run this LG refrigerator inverters in power cut","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"GIYAS AHMED","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it delivered fast","answer":"Within 6days","votes":"0","username":"Jaleel ck","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"kiya yea solar sai b chalti hai","answer":"Yes bro","votes":"0","username":"Pipash das","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Delivery person told that technician will do installation, when do the technician will come?","answer":"Installation is not provided,  leave the fridge unattended for a minimum of 3hrs for the internal oil and gas to settle and then switch on the fridge,  by doing this the performance of fridge will be good","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Door size or dimensions?","answer":"DIMENSIONS (W X D X H) (MM)","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"In retail shops we get 10 years warranty why is not mentioned here","answer":"10 year warranty on compressor only, and it is mentioned on warranty card.","votes":"0","username":"Jaleel ck","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"State the power","answer":"48 Watt. Total consumption in a year . 104 kilowatt hour. 90-310v","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH PANDEY","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is fredge back is open","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"AMAR KUMAR PANDEY","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the storage capacity of refrigerator for food","answer":"190 L, for a small family of 3 or 4 it's sufficient","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"If no installation service is provided for some day can we ask reduced rate?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Return policy","answer":"10days from the delivery date.","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"If we put this refrigerator in poor ventilated room, does it have any adverse effect?","answer":"Definitely it will have bad effects,  so keep the fridge in ventilated area but away from sun light","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has dry storage in shiny silver one","answer":"Not specifically,  if needed wrap the required item in a double polythene.","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have door cooling?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it delivery including installation on same day","answer":"May be next working day","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"power  of motor in watts?","answer":"Details are provided in product description.","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to raise warranty on this product","answer":"Preseve your order invoice,  that can be used for any warranty issue","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does Amazon provide open and check product for physical damages before delivery","answer":"Yes, we have to do the open box inspection,  if no damage then only we should accept the product,  till then do not share the delivery OTP to the delivery associate","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Total hight of including stand","answer":"Please see seller's specifications","votes":"0","username":"NARENDRABABU YAKKALA","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long will the ice be frozen in this fridge?","answer":"Very nice refizer","votes":"0","username":"Gurmelsingh","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get fridge handle ?","answer":"May be","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Autocut option available?","answer":"Yes it's one.of the built in option in a fridge","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"i have received semi defrost. why it is semi ? i ordered fully defrost. And no where it mentioned semi defrost on product details. what the hell amazo","answer":"You need to contact Amazon customer support","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"We did not recd base stand","answer":"Contact customer care","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"2022 star reating?","answer":"3","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"year of manufacture ?","answer":"2021 you can purchase blindly awesome product","votes":"0","username":"Anand","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who will provide warrenty for this product? Is that amazon send a warrenty card?","answer":"No one sends warranty, we can take advantage of warranty from the bill.","votes":"0","username":"Gopal Ram","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many design s in red colour","answer":"2","votes":"0","username":"Mandar Patil","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need a 165 ltr refrigerator. Can you show me one of good brand?","answer":"Go for LG","votes":"0","username":"Anand","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is required Inverter or without inverter?","answer":"Work on both with or without inverter.","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH PANDEY","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get single door refrigiratoroor with back side closed","answer":"Not completely closed posible.","votes":"0","username":"shantanu kumar das","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product require the any stabilizer required","answer":"stabilizer not required for this product inbuilt stabilizer disined by LG,","votes":"0","username":"N priyanivas","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many years warranty or guarantee","answer":"One year and 10 year on compresure.","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH PANDEY","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is Door cooling or no","answer":"No it's not the door cooling one.","votes":"0","username":"Anand Arjunaha","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is this offer duration?","answer":"1 years + 10 years compressor","votes":"0","username":"mohd r.","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40241cfba6a7877c13a1"},"product_asin":"B06XG9N37B","QAs":[{"question":"Exchange available","answer":"I have no discount","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40241cfba6a7877c13a3"},"product_asin":"B084PPZXBX","QAs":[{"question":"month and year of manufacture?","answer":"Normally it should be same as you purchase in local shops. As most of authorised sellers in Amazon will directly order to company and company will deliver from your nearest godown.","votes":"0","username":"srikanth ch","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it door stainless steel?","answer":"Not stainless.","votes":"0","username":"gopalakrishna","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40251cfba6a7877c13a6"},"product_asin":"B07612F52G","QAs":[{"question":"Is this display pannel working","answer":"Yes , display panel works it shows the temperature of refrigerator and freezer.... it disappears after 20seconds after closing the door..","votes":"0","username":"Annu","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the door dimension when open??","answer":"91+65","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to Stop The Freezer?","answer":"you cant","votes":"0","username":"Sandeep","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40251cfba6a7877c13b1"},"product_asin":"B084S8LB1D","QAs":[{"question":"How much discount you will give if i pay prepayment","answer":"No I have no discount.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40261cfba6a7877c13b4"},"product_asin":"B08X14KW3R","QAs":[{"question":"Procedure to claim warranty?","answer":"Pls check the toll free number on carton/manual or sticker and call to register your complaint. You will be contacted by authorized service personnel to plan appointment to visit and accept complaint.","votes":"0","username":"Sunil Panchbhai","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it make ice?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SHYAM HOME ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we store milk","answer":"Yes  and if any quiry call me on this number 7014579722","votes":"0","username":"SHYAM HOME ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 1star or 2star?","answer":"2 star","votes":"0","username":"SHYAM HOME ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has a freezer?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SHYAM HOME ELECTRONICS","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40261cfba6a7877c13b8"},"product_asin":"B079QNTQ84","QAs":[{"question":"Can we plug this to a 16amp plug point? pls advise","answer":"You can plug 16anp also","votes":"0","username":"surya","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it run on home inverter when no power supply?","answer":"Yes 90v above means you can run","votes":"0","username":"surya","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much Watts taking this product","answer":"90v to 240v","votes":"0","username":"surya","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it automatic defrost ?","answer":"No, it's manual","votes":"0","username":"surya","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 5 star refrigerator or 4 star? Mentioned 5 star but sticker is 4 star , why?","answer":"It's a 4 star refrigerator. When I brought it was showing 4 star only.","votes":"0","username":"Soumyayan Paladhi","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will this be delivered to 2nd floor building without lift?","answer":"Yes it can be delivered to 2nd floor, if the stairs are fairly spaced.","votes":"0","username":"Soumyayan Paladhi","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"If it got repaired  then what to do","answer":"You can contact the manufacturer directly, the details are mentioned in the product brochure.","votes":"0","username":"Soumyayan Paladhi","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Come with the stand","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Soumyayan Paladhi","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which material gasket is used in this refrigerator : silicon or rubber?","answer":"Silicon.","votes":"0","username":"Soumyayan Paladhi","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it frost free.? Do we need to keep defrosting?","answer":"Yes you have to defrost the machine after every 7days.","votes":"0","username":"Soumyayan Paladhi","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40271cfba6a7877c13c3"},"product_asin":"B08W9BRBMP","QAs":[{"question":"Do we need to remove the water manually when we defrost or it dry automatically ?","answer":"No need to dry manually. But you should do the defrost operation twice a week compulsory.","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh E","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to now the manufacturing year of the product","answer":"Best product","votes":"0","username":"Gunjan","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stand available with this product?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh E","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the year and month of model","answer":"05/2022","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh E","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40271cfba6a7877c13c8"},"product_asin":"B088QGY2G5","QAs":[{"question":"How much storage volume","answer":"220 Litres.","votes":"0","username":"Prodipta Mukherjee","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Auto defrost available???","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Prodipta Mukherjee","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we store dry fruits","answer":"Yes. Why not.","votes":"0","username":"Prodipta Mukherjee","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product description says it is purple colour but in the product description it has pink colour. what colour would it come ?","answer":"Its a combination of pink and Purple. Mostly purple","votes":"0","username":"Prodipta Mukherjee","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Gross volume and storage volumn.","answer":"235 Litres and 220 Litres.","votes":"0","username":"Prodipta Mukherjee","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Power consumption per year?","answer":"power consumption -300 watt per day or 110kw per annum. note to reduce power cosumption by a fridge try to reduce door opening and closing nos per day. never keep open the fridge door close it as early as possible. LG IS BEST ENERGY EFFICIENT SO FAR IDENTIFIED. I AM USING ONE 1.5 TON 5STAR 2022 MAKE SPLIT A.C THAT ALSO CONSUMING LESS THAN 3KW PER DAY-15 HOURS OPERATING PER DAY. CARE VERY SOON ENERGY COST WILL GO UP.see less","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Need to buy inverter separately?","answer":"I AM NOT A LG SALES MAN, ASK TO LG DIRECTLY.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the manufacturing year?","answer":"EVERY DAY REFRIGERATION TECHNOLOGY IS GETTING CHANGED.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there light bulb inside","answer":"YES THERE IS A LIGHT, BUT IT IS NOT ILLUMINATING ENTIRE FRIDGE.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Power connection kitana hai","answer":"QUESTION IT SELF CONFUSING, MAY BE POWER COSUMPTION KITNA HAI.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40271cfba6a7877c13dd"},"product_asin":"B08W8TJ3FM","QAs":[{"question":"What is the manufacturing year?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"RAHUL","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40281cfba6a7877c13df"},"product_asin":"B084Y86B9Z","QAs":[{"question":"what dilvery time take","answer":"25days","votes":"0","username":"Tushar Ubale","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Year of manufacture?","answer":"2020 I think","votes":"0","username":"Tushar Ubale","date":"2022-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"This fridge have keylock","answer":"Yes have key lock","votes":"0","username":"Yogesh…","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Inverter compressor and non inverter compressor","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Yogesh…","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Lock system is available","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Yogesh…","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many hours of cooling when the power cut ???","answer":"7hrs","votes":"0","username":"Yogesh…","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it need stabilizer??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Yogesh…","date":"2022-05-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it automatic defrosting?","answer":"No, defrosting is not automatic, need to low down.","votes":"0","username":"Gurdeep Chhimpa","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40281cfba6a7877c13e9"},"product_asin":"B07W7B94GZ","QAs":[{"question":"This fridge has 2 temparature controllers or 1 temperature control","answer":"One temperature control regulator only.","votes":"0","username":"LOWEST PRICE IN TN","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40281cfba6a7877c13eb"},"product_asin":"B083JN87RJ","QAs":[{"question":"In chef mode, the freezer converts to normal fridge?","answer":"Hi,","votes":"0","username":"Amit","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have coolpack in it???","answer":"Don't go for this fridge. Opt for LG or Samsung instead","votes":"0","username":"Gautam Jaiswal","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Shelves are toughened glass or not?","answer":"Yes they are... I have bought the same refrigerator","votes":"0","username":"Priyanka yelve","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have seperate air vent for refrigerator section and freezer section","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Priyanka yelve","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will delivery people deliver the fridge to 2nd floor","answer":"Yes I stay in 3rd floor it can be delivered bought the same fridge","votes":"0","username":"Priyanka yelve","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40291cfba6a7877c13ee"},"product_asin":"B091Q3T3KQ","QAs":[{"question":"What is the year of manufacturing","answer":"All is good mast cooling no problem","votes":"0","username":"PRITHVI RAj","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i order which year modle i get?","answer":"Good product","votes":"0","username":"PRITHVI RAj","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is period of compressor guaranty","answer":"10 yeas","votes":"0","username":"PRITHVI RAj","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the freezer door jam due to formation of ice? isn't their a risk of breaking the hinge of the door?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PRITHVI RAj","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"5 amp or 15 amp plug point required?","answer":"5amp","votes":"0","username":"PRITHVI RAj","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is exchange is available in rajkot?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"PRITHVI RAj","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will this fridge make warning sound if fridge is opened more than 5min?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PRITHVI RAj","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40291cfba6a7877c13f6"},"product_asin":"B07NBZ43PH","QAs":[{"question":"Would Amazon will deliver to 1st floor, if stair case if little conjected","answer":"No. Iam disappointed with the delivery","votes":"0","username":"Phani Sharath","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the star rating of this fridge?","answer":"5 star","votes":"0","username":"Chethan","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"1 year me kitna unit hota he..","answer":"Iam not using separate meter for this.","votes":"0","username":"R………u","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Steplizer free operation?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Phani Sharath","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this available in mirror white?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Phani Sharath","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"No service company Whirlpool","answer":"Call on their toll-free number dude, they send a technician on the same day.","votes":"0","username":"Sol","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the star rating as per BEE?","answer":"It is good condition","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the lower part gets cool?","answer":"Yes it has it's own seperate cooling part but don't have lighting.","votes":"0","username":"Alok Ray","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why so many negative comments? Is this seller is sending damaged products?","answer":"No i got fresh piece","votes":"0","username":"Consumer","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"No one is there to pick up a call in one assist is it true ? I had experience 3 hours waiting from registered contact number and no one is there to as","answer":"No it is not true","votes":"0","username":"Consumer","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"The middle  section doesn't open. How to do that?","answer":"Refer YouTube video or contect technician","votes":"0","username":"Consumer","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402a1cfba6a7877c13fd"},"product_asin":"B08CS3FKFY","QAs":[{"question":"Stabilizer needer?","answer":"no need  stabilizers.","votes":"0","username":"syed muktiyar","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model it is","answer":"Manufacturing date given as Mar-2022","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Light white or yellow","answer":"Not yellow","votes":"0","username":"V RAMBABU","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402a1cfba6a7877c1401"},"product_asin":"B084XMM69M","QAs":[{"question":"I think half Air vents not working please tell me ..how much pressure of air from air vents","answer":"First freezer temperature set to recommend (Set to middle ) and second door side set to normal then your fridge 50 % -50% cooling freezer & bottom part when you make ice then you set freezer high otherwise set to normal","votes":"0","username":"Ghanshyam Tiwari","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do it has an automatic door","answer":"No it doesn't have automatic door. You need to do it manually.","votes":"0","username":"Aashiq Saifi","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402c1cfba6a7877c1406"},"product_asin":"B083KSSS1H","QAs":[{"question":"Installation required or not ?","answer":"Installation required.","votes":"0","username":"sumantra357","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the coustmer care no of whirlpool refrigerator.","answer":"In your invoice.","votes":"0","username":"sumantra357","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Contact amazon customer care?","answer":"You can.","votes":"0","username":"sumantra357","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this returnable","answer":"Replacement only.","votes":"0","username":"sumantra357","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i return the refrigerator","answer":"Replacement only.","votes":"0","username":"sumantra357","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"When the Installation will be done?","answer":"After delivery.","votes":"0","username":"sumantra357","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402c1cfba6a7877c140d"},"product_asin":"B083JNJRS5","QAs":[{"question":"Can we conect in house invertor","answer":"No, we can not connect with inverter. It shows overloaded","votes":"0","username":"sanju gautam","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty how many years?","answer":"10 yrs but don't buy, not as expected. It is not frost free.","votes":"0","username":"sanju gautam","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What this product mrp in teg","answer":"26999","votes":"0","username":"Muhamad Saqif","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it possible to prepone delivery instead of current schedule?","answer":"my opinion is NO..but you have to check with Amazon Care","votes":"0","username":"Muhamad Saqif","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"If any technical problem is happen then","answer":"This is good quality product. hope no technical issues happen. Warranty covers only certain set of items.","votes":"0","username":"Muhamad Saqif","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402c1cfba6a7877c1419"},"product_asin":"B083KVTQ6Z","QAs":[{"question":"Is it auto defrost","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"rakesh dave","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402d1cfba6a7877c141d"},"product_asin":"B07NBZSVCL","QAs":[{"question":"It work on home ups","answer":"No it's can damage the ups","votes":"0","username":"Chandra prakash Mathur","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"BEE Energy rating ?(please don't give CFL rating answer)","answer":"Yes it is.","votes":"0","username":"dip","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402e1cfba6a7877c141f"},"product_asin":"B0892Q3WBW","QAs":[{"question":"Can u provide one more glass shelf","answer":"You got to ask the question from a seller; I guess he may charge you some extra buck for it.","votes":"0","username":"Anil","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there requirement for deforst ?","answer":"All time","votes":"0","username":"Anil","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the watt of the freeze?","answer":"Standard time","votes":"0","username":"Anil","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Zero down payment available","answer":"Sure","votes":"0","username":"Anil","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402e1cfba6a7877c1424"},"product_asin":"B078YHT1FR","QAs":[{"question":"Rang bataye","answer":"Stop buying this suitable for show case not for house day to day storage activities .think before buy visit the shop then order","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 5 Star rating refrigerator?","answer":"Ye sits declared 5 star but costly","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i lock the door of freez","answer":"Not satisfied storage is very worst . Either too much cooling or low .vegitables and leads are wasted .I will advise not to buy .only for showcase purpose .waste of money","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want red colour fridge whirpool 240 litrewith exchange offer","answer":"No go with other option . Because of 3 thousand you will fed in future","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"If thise thermocol which is placed under the fridge..have to remove?","answer":"Need to remove","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it automatic on and off","answer":"Yes cooling cit off on and off is there in addition install a stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Without credit card EMi hai","answer":"With out credit !","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want change delivery address","answer":"Change update to Amazon and seller","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to know the exact delivery location","answer":"Share the location as per your current location in Amazon address","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you delivered on my doorstep","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402e1cfba6a7877c1427"},"product_asin":"B09PMPK18J","QAs":[{"question":"inbuilt stabilizer is there or need to be connected externally ???","answer":"Inbuilt is there","votes":"0","username":"vignesh","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Back grill covered ?","answer":"Free","votes":"0","username":"aravind sain","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Gst invoice available?","answer":"Free","votes":"0","username":"aravind sain","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402e1cfba6a7877c142b"},"product_asin":"B083RPPSQF","QAs":[{"question":"Is this refrigerator slightly tilted or lean towards backside?","answer":"Not in my Fridge or I didn't notice. But I face sometimes oil ya grease liking from the door. but overall good.","votes":"0","username":"Anwar Ali","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's the colour of this fridge. Gray or Black?","answer":"Gray","votes":"0","username":"Amit","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Refrigerator ke andar ki light yellow hai ya white acctuly yellow light achi nahi lagti hai","answer":"Yellow hai unfortunately.","votes":"0","username":"Akash","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402f1cfba6a7877c142d"},"product_asin":"B083KVZQ7Z","QAs":[{"question":"Who much Warranty?","answer":"10 years compressor","votes":"0","username":"Vijay  pal","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Delivery possible in kudal , kokan pincode 416520??","answer":"Check in AMAZON app.","votes":"0","username":"PARAMESH...TN","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Star rating is 2022 year","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PARAMESH...TN","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the exact storage volume ?Is 192 gross volume ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"PARAMESH...TN","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402f1cfba6a7877c1432"},"product_asin":"B09PMTJPPQ","QAs":[{"question":"I didnt get warranty card??","answer":"Invoice is work as warrenty card","votes":"0","username":"Nunu","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf402f1cfba6a7877c1434"},"product_asin":"B078YJXPCF","QAs":[{"question":"Can we get an extra egg tray?","answer":"Pls ask the dealer.","votes":"0","username":"Prachi Vashisht","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"which type of compressor","answer":"Check product details.","votes":"0","username":"Prachi Vashisht","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the inside capacity?","answer":"Around 300 litres","votes":"0","username":"Prachi Vashisht","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"It have a inverter?????","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Prachi Vashisht","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Firdge in lock","answer":"No lock 🔒 available....but it's not require... because we don't keep money & gold.","votes":"0","username":"Santanu Manna(9609214938)","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"star rat","answer":"Check product details.","votes":"0","username":"Prachi Vashisht","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"The back side of the refrigerator is covered entirely ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Prachi Vashisht","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which compressor type reciprocatery compressor or normal compressor","answer":"Check product details.","votes":"0","username":"Prachi Vashisht","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any long term users? Please give review. Bcz mlst of all telling its not working after 2yrs? Is it","answer":"I have had multidoor whirlpool ( the older model) for over 10 years and never had any issues. I lent it to my relative and brought the new one. No doubly about its long term efficacy. Just go for it.","votes":"0","username":"Satish Kumar k v","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40301cfba6a7877c1448"},"product_asin":"B09PMTDDLR","QAs":[{"question":"inbuilt stabilizer is there or need to be connected externally ???","answer":"Inbuilt is there","votes":"0","username":"vignesh","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Back grill covered ?","answer":"Free","votes":"0","username":"aravind sain","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Gst invoice available?","answer":"Free","votes":"0","username":"aravind sain","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40311cfba6a7877c144c"},"product_asin":"B091Q56ZR8","QAs":[{"question":"Is this product having sound for opening doors for more time","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Swapnali korale","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any additional warrenty on compressor","answer":"No but we can take with additional charges","votes":"0","username":"Swapnali korale","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40311cfba6a7877c144e"},"product_asin":"B078YL5K8D","QAs":[{"question":"What is consumption of electricity. Less than 60 watt is very confusing.","answer":"Don't buy this fridge. It stopped working after 4 days of installation. When reported to Customer care, they dint not respond to calls for a week. Frustrated with all these we returned the fridge. After 2 days of return, technician calls to ask what is the issue, can we come for repair.","votes":"0","username":"Phani Krishna","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this matt finishing refrigerator","answer":"Appears like Matt but not really","votes":"0","username":"Phani Krishna","date":"2022-05-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40311cfba6a7877c1451"},"product_asin":"B083KRV6DK","QAs":[{"question":"Is it frost ftee?","answer":"No. It is frost forming fridge. Defrost button given. Need to use it every 3-4 days.","votes":"0","username":"syed yaseen","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty of compressr","answer":"10 years warranty given on compressor.","votes":"0","username":"syed yaseen","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this product have inverter compressor or normal one ?","answer":"NORMAL ONE","votes":"0","username":"RAMA CHANDRAN","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stayblezer wanted","answer":"Yes required. U need to buy","votes":"0","username":"syed yaseen","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many year compressor warnty","answer":"10","votes":"0","username":"syed yaseen","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why Handdle not given on this product","answer":"Groove given","votes":"0","username":"syed yaseen","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Inbuilt stabilizer or not?","answer":"No. Buy a stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"syed yaseen","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40321cfba6a7877c1457"},"product_asin":"B086H3NR1F","QAs":[{"question":"Where can I found adjustable legs?","answer":"I couldn't find it, there is a drawer below, I just put a stand below the refrigerator","votes":"0","username":"SANDIP NANDI","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Total how many years of warranty?","answer":"10 years","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the capacity 215 L is including the bottom tray?","answer":"Looks like I made a bad decision to buy this without knowing that it has manual defroze water collection . Every time being a senior citizen can't move fridge physically to drain defroze water.  Any correspondance with CC no use.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wifi connect this refrigerator","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Raghuraman","date":"2022-04-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which of the year model","answer":"Label period 1Jan 2020-31Dec 2021 .means 2021 model.","votes":"0","username":"Raj Royal","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to take off door rack","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Raj Royal","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is Openbox delivery","answer":"Means Amazon courier person visit at home and open box.","votes":"0","username":"Raj Royal","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"No invois","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Raj Royal","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to select colors  order time","answer":"Select option is available on buy now option uper side","votes":"0","username":"Raj Royal","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which of the year model","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Shiva Kumar","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"ಸ್ಟೇಬ್ಲೆಜಾರ್ ಫ್ರೀ","answer":"in built stabilizer adopted. not stabiliser free","votes":"0","username":"sathya","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much watt ?","answer":"Fridge ki width Kam hai","votes":"0","username":"Ravi","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Back is covered or not?","answer":"Not","votes":"0","username":"AMIT  RAJ","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40321cfba6a7877c145c"},"product_asin":"B0982Y9C1C","QAs":[{"question":"Is this operate by electronic or inverter","answer":"It operates in electrical power.","votes":"0","username":"Vinayak jadhav","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"It has back foot or not","answer":"You have to put a stand on which freezer stand. Call service centre.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Condensor grill is bent at the centre bottom. Is this a defect or that is how it is designed?","answer":"Its diffect","votes":"0","username":"deep","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why emi available","answer":"For easy payment","votes":"0","username":"Tanu…","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which compress used","answer":"Inverter compressor used","votes":"0","username":"Vinayak jadhav","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why cooling not done","answer":"Good cooling..","votes":"0","username":"Rajesh Wadhwani","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it frost free?","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"Tanu…","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Backsite panel coverd or open","answer":"Open","votes":"0","username":"Tanu…","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"On which date should i pay the emi?","answer":"Depend your bank policy..","votes":"0","username":"Rajesh Wadhwani","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What if this is delivered broken or damage body? Is this will be replace without any extra cost and without extra transportation charges?","answer":"Is it replaced before accepting. at delivery.","votes":"0","username":"Vinayak jadhav","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi, please revert on urgent basis. I have 190litre fridge which I like to exchange however on the left exterior wall there is dent.can I exchange .","answer":"Not exchange offer given","votes":"0","username":"Vinayak jadhav","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"water leakage problem","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Vinayak jadhav","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Refrigerator key include or not","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Harsh S Shetiya","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to put legs of the fridge. I can't make sense out of it. I thought product was damaged","answer":"Call the service centre. You have to buy stand with Rs1000/-","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Written here 1195 centimetres height is that true?","answer":"Nice","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which year model","answer":"Super","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Backside coiled are closed or not?","answer":"Exlent","votes":"0","username":"Kuldeep","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40331cfba6a7877c146d"},"product_asin":"B07G5YV3LC","QAs":[{"question":"Will it work for samsung 700 l (rs72r5001m9tl) side-by-side fridge?","answer":"It adjustable so it should work.","votes":"0","username":"BaluMahendra","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hi will this product can use for Samsung 394 ltr refrigerator","answer":"Yes it should work as it is adjustable we. Can adjust accordingly to our requirements.","votes":"0","username":"pabi","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this suitable for semi automatic washing machine","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"BaluMahendra","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitalbe for symphony storm 100 litre cooler?","answer":"Very very bad","votes":"0","username":"ATITA DEY","date":"2022-07-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it available height/depth in 9 inches","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ATITA DEY","date":"2022-07-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it suitalbe for symphony storm 100 litre cooler?","answer":"Yes sir its suitable","votes":"0","username":"Valianto Retailer","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40341cfba6a7877c1471"},"product_asin":"B08SBSL8Y2","QAs":[{"question":"Is it convertible","answer":"No it is not convertible.","votes":"0","username":"Mumbai M45","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is model m 1°c pr bottle m pani cool hone m kitna time lgta h","answer":"less than 5 mins.","votes":"0","username":"nikhat n.","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"When your engineer comes for demo","answer":"next day","votes":"0","username":"nikhat n.","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer needed in 2021 model?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Riddle","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does 2.25lt cool drink fit vertically ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Kumar","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the loading capacity ?","answer":"it's written 253 L but it feels like 200 L give or take","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the power consumption?","answer":"Haven't checked it yet as the fridge is just over a month old.","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Katte","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"This colour is in matt finish or in glossy?","answer":"Glossy","votes":"0","username":"BAKUL BENZZAMIN","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year ?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"BAKUL BENZZAMIN","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i bay this ref in this year","answer":"yes you can","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"compressor power in watts?","answer":"depends on the star rating","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to convert freezer to fridge","answer":"Available only in convertible models","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"year of manufacture","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are you providing open box inspection upon delivery, installation not required?","answer":"Be sure to inspect any physical damage on delivery by opening ,later when Samsung comes for trial then it will be difficult to return because amazon will say you accepted delivery and gave code,Samsung will say delivery damages are not covered by Samsung…so u will be caught in between..inspect thoroughly physical damage by microscopesee less","votes":"0","username":"RAJESH P.","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is extended  warranty  helpful?","answer":"if you face frequent voltage fluctuations","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is extended warranty  hèlpful?","answer":"nope","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i buy it in installment?","answer":"sure. emi option is available","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is return option available?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Need delivery at my society Ajnara homes greater Noida west pin code 201318, it is showing not available in this area, any reason??","answer":"Check with other sellers","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is power , watts  , kwhr/yr ?","answer":"Varies from model to model. Check the description","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it double door or single door?","answer":"Double door","votes":"0","username":"md.Aslam khan","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the installation required from Samsung executive or we can open the item","answer":"You can inspect the product(dent/colour) at delivery time if ok you can pluge in after 2/3 hours after delivery because of cooling gas.","votes":"0","username":"Praful Gogari","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cash on delivery is not supported but i get it ob cash on delivery","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"I get it cash on delivery method","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this refigerator works on  850VA  single battery home inverter? What is the maximum starting current  or wattage of this refegerator?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"nikhat n.","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fridge side panels are too heating. Is there any prblm","answer":"Side panels were heating,and there is no cooling effect on refrigerator side","votes":"0","username":"md.Aslam khan","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get cod with pin 711302","answer":"Please check it in delevery options","votes":"0","username":"Ghanshyam","date":"2022-06-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Payment is cancelled? When i get my refund back","answer":"contact customer care service","votes":"0","username":"nikhat n.","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Double door fridge 2022","answer":"this is the best","votes":"0","username":"nikhat n.","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is fresh room compartment is a closed box with or is it just a open box?","answer":"Open box like ....depend on your uses","votes":"0","username":"Anshuman","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"For how long fruits and vegetables are kept fresh?","answer":"I hv tried for around a week... No problem.... More than that i hv not tired","votes":"0","username":"Mumbai M45","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whats the procedure for installation, incase if we go ahead and buy this?","answer":"Simply follow the instructions. A technician from the company will visit for installation.","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Katte","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"For how long fruits and vegetables are kept fresh?","answer":"It depends on how you store these items. It will last a couple of weeks if you store it in food-grade airtight plastic containers.","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Katte","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this need any stabiliser","answer":"No stabiliser is needed as it can withstand wide power fluctions.","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Katte","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be the thing's done during Installation/demo, Is Installation chargeable or do they sell any market products while visiting","answer":"They will try and sell their products in addition to installing the equipment (an excuse).","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Katte","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i exchange my old fridge??","answer":"Don’t try - pick up guys will reject with many stories and u will end up paying 2500 cash","votes":"0","username":"Harris","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the manufacturing year of this refrigerator?","answer":"2021-2022","votes":"0","username":"Harris","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want it to be delivered to 2nd floor using stairs, will delivery be done ? I don't want to argue delivery person during delivery. How can I make sur","answer":"No problem","votes":"0","username":"Harris","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dimensions by width, depth and height","answer":"As mentioned","votes":"0","username":"Harris","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"When u say “runs on solar energy “ wht do u mean","answer":"Will work in","votes":"0","username":"Harris","date":"2022-07-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can in the frezzer bharaf ghamega sab jagh se","answer":"No freezer may bharaf nahi ghamega sab jagha se.","votes":"0","username":"Balasubramaniam R","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange  change available on 700059 pincode","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Balasubramaniam R","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it run only on solar energy or electricity also","answer":"It runs in electricity. I don't know about solar energy because I don't have solar power","votes":"0","username":"Balasubramaniam R","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40341cfba6a7877c147c"},"product_asin":"B091TZ4TNZ","QAs":[{"question":"Does it come with an egg tray?","answer":"Yes it does come with an egg tray for 8 eggs.","votes":"0","username":"Sunil Desai","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Voltage mentioned as 135v is it suitable for india? indians standard 230v-240v.. please confirm.","answer":"Such models are claimed to work even with ac power supply of as low as 135V and as high as 290V , meaning such model , as claimed, works nicely without the need of connecting any external voltage stabilizer even in worst possible fluctuating voltage situation which may sometimes prevail in some places of our country. Obviously therefore,  such models is supposed to work, without any problem ,under normal power supply situation like 230-240V.see less","votes":"0","username":"peters","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this convertible","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sunil Desai","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it auto connect to home inverter after power cut?","answer":"A refrigerator works on whatever  power supply it's connected to. Your inverter connection should be wired by your electrician such  that it can feed the concerned power points when main supply goes off. It's a very easy work for any electrician.","votes":"0","username":"peters","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"After power cut, cooling remains for how long?","answer":"That'll depend upon how many times you open the freezer door.. during no power supply situation ... according to common experience, if the refrigerator door is not opened for more than once or twice, when there's no power and not more than 5-10 seconds on each occasion, reasonable coolness can be preserved  for several hours.","votes":"0","username":"peters","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much power it consumes when on home inverter?","answer":"The refrigerator will consume same  power  from inverter as it cosumes from mains supply.. however depending on your inverter efficient, net power consumed by the refrigerator plus inverter will be definitely higher than when the refrigerator works directly from main commercial supply","votes":"0","username":"peters","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it auto connect to inverter?","answer":"The inverter should be so wired by the electrician that the inverter can feed the refrigerator power supply.. it's very easy for any electrician.","votes":"0","username":"peters","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it possible to convert the freezer into fridge and shutdown the main fridge?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sunil Desai","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40341cfba6a7877c1486"},"product_asin":"B08448TTJM","QAs":[{"question":"Can we convert freezer into fridge?","answer":"Yes.. You can.","votes":"0","username":"Ankit Jain","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do they delivery to 2 floor","answer":"Yes.. They do.","votes":"0","username":"Ankit Jain","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you give delivery to 3 floor climbing the stair case","answer":"They delivered to my house on 3rd floor, using staircase.","votes":"0","username":"Ankit Jain","date":"2022-06-27 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40361cfba6a7877c1492"},"product_asin":"B07R9NJMGB","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have shelves in the door? Address please","answer":"Hii there... It does have all the shelves nd everything but it is a pathetic product and this is a pathetic brand i hv recently bought it nd there is no cooling in the lower compartment i hv to throw away so many food items since i hv got this i have been raising complaints about it and calling customer service but they r just sitting nd doing nothing so pls do not buy thissee less","votes":"0","username":"soham sharma","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"411L not in stock. When will it come back in stock","answer":"Even if it comes in stocks, dont buy it. very bad and horrible product","votes":"0","username":"Salman Razzaq","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"The cooling coil pipe is made of copper","answer":"Wrost experience with this Refrigerator","votes":"0","username":"Expert Advice","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who manufactured 411l model? Stablizer required?","answer":"Hi - Please avoid buying this brand and product completely, to save 1-5k rupees dont go for it. I bought this as a gift for my sister and in less than 25 days it started having issues and amazon doesnt want to refund it and until now i have requested for technical/service support for 18 times but no one turned up despite everyday they say they will send some one. Thank me later.see less","votes":"0","username":"Salman Razzaq","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Freezer capacity?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Expert Advice","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is it's model number?","answer":"Hii there... It does have all the shelves nd everything but it is a pathetic product and this is a pathetic brand i hv recently bought it nd there is no cooling in the lower compartment i hv to throw away so many food items since i hv got this i have been raising complaints about it and calling customer service but they r just sitting nd doing nothing so pls do not buy thissee less","votes":"0","username":"soham sharma","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why not available exchange offer in my location 632105","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Anita M.","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Want to know How was the cooling of this refrigirator bcz i have order one. Did i made a good choice or mistake? I have tine till 26 april to cancel .","answer":"I am using this refrigerator from 1 month. Everything is good so far. No complaints. Good Product.","votes":"0","username":"NR","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there warranty on compressor? If yes, for how many years?","answer":"5 yrs of warranty","votes":"0","username":"NR","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about service? Where n whom to contact for servicing, and where's it's service center?","answer":"Hii there... It does have all the shelves nd everything but it is a pathetic product and this is a pathetic brand i hv recently bought it nd there is no cooling in the lower compartment i hv to throw away so many food items since i hv got this i have been raising complaints about it and calling customer service but they r just sitting nd doing nothing so pls do not buy thissee less","votes":"0","username":"soham sharma","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whats exact dimensions of 411ltr which is different from 345ltr....? In the description shown same sizes in picture","answer":"Hii there... It does have all the shelves nd everything but it is a pathetic product and this is a pathetic brand i hv recently bought it nd there is no cooling in the lower compartment i hv to throw away so many food items since i hv got this i have been raising complaints about it and calling customer service but they r just sitting nd doing nothing so pls do not buy thissee less","votes":"0","username":"soham sharma","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I reverse the door for left hand users","answer":"Hello - forget reversing, don’t buy this product. We faced a lot of issues and finally after 40 days we managed to return the product. It took us 98 calls and 50 service call promises and they never came. But with warranty from showroom and not online.","votes":"0","username":"Salman Razzaq","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it convertible ?","answer":"No, not convertible","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Shourie","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it silent or noisy?","answer":"not very noisy. not absolutely silent. it makes a little sound but does not disturb.","votes":"0","username":"Jayar","date":"2022-07-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it silent or noisy","answer":"Silent","votes":"0","username":"Kiran","date":"2022-07-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange offer?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ابن شفیع الحسامی","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40361cfba6a7877c149d"},"product_asin":"B08VSB3V64","QAs":[{"question":"Is the freezer frost free?","answer":"yes very nice freezer you can buy","votes":"0","username":"pankaj","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40371cfba6a7877c14ab"},"product_asin":"B08X72GY5Q","QAs":[{"question":"Is there any fridge auto defrost without water collecting tray","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"mohd r.","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the connected power for this Fridge??","answer":"Maybye 198 units per year","votes":"0","username":"mohd r.","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many days door delivery","answer":"3 to 5 days","votes":"0","username":"mohd r.","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whatvis the difference between convertible refrigerator and non convertible refrigerator??","answer":"U can convert your freezer to non freezer","votes":"0","username":"Nishil.SB","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Amazon Gift card are accepted","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"mohd r.","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Convertible refrigerator means?","answer":"Convertible means,you can use the upper unit as a normal refrigerator or as a ice chamber.","votes":"0","username":"Satya Mohapatra","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's Dorcooling are not","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vinodkumar","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year of this product gl-i292rozx (date of question 09/06/2022)","answer":"April 2022","votes":"0","username":"Jaleel ck","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much electricity power is used in 24hrs fridge","answer":"Year-1500k","votes":"0","username":"Pipash das","date":"2022-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year please?? Seems pretty old and that might change the power rating?","answer":"April 2022","votes":"0","username":"Jaleel ck","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is one year warranty??","answer":"One year warranty for ligt weight parts covered under warranty. But no need anything, it is best working refrigerator so far in my case. No Electrical consumption, minimal charges","votes":"0","username":"Dr.T. Alwarsamy ,Ph.D ( Engg .…","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we run this LG refrigerator inverters in power cut","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"GIYAS AHMED","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it delivered fast","answer":"Within 6days","votes":"0","username":"Jaleel ck","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"kiya yea solar sai b chalti hai","answer":"Yes bro","votes":"0","username":"Pipash das","date":"2022-05-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Delivery person told that technician will do installation, when do the technician will come?","answer":"Installation is not provided,  leave the fridge unattended for a minimum of 3hrs for the internal oil and gas to settle and then switch on the fridge,  by doing this the performance of fridge will be good","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Door size or dimensions?","answer":"DIMENSIONS (W X D X H) (MM)","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"In retail shops we get 10 years warranty why is not mentioned here","answer":"10 year warranty on compressor only, and it is mentioned on warranty card.","votes":"0","username":"Jaleel ck","date":"2022-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"State the power","answer":"48 Watt. Total consumption in a year . 104 kilowatt hour. 90-310v","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH PANDEY","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is fredge back is open","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"AMAR KUMAR PANDEY","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the storage capacity of refrigerator for food","answer":"190 L, for a small family of 3 or 4 it's sufficient","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"If no installation service is provided for some day can we ask reduced rate?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Return policy","answer":"10days from the delivery date.","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"If we put this refrigerator in poor ventilated room, does it have any adverse effect?","answer":"Definitely it will have bad effects,  so keep the fridge in ventilated area but away from sun light","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has dry storage in shiny silver one","answer":"Not specifically,  if needed wrap the required item in a double polythene.","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have door cooling?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it delivery including installation on same day","answer":"May be next working day","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"power  of motor in watts?","answer":"Details are provided in product description.","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to raise warranty on this product","answer":"Preseve your order invoice,  that can be used for any warranty issue","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does Amazon provide open and check product for physical damages before delivery","answer":"Yes, we have to do the open box inspection,  if no damage then only we should accept the product,  till then do not share the delivery OTP to the delivery associate","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Total hight of including stand","answer":"Please see seller's specifications","votes":"0","username":"NARENDRABABU YAKKALA","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"How long will the ice be frozen in this fridge?","answer":"Very nice refizer","votes":"0","username":"Gurmelsingh","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get fridge handle ?","answer":"May be","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Autocut option available?","answer":"Yes it's one.of the built in option in a fridge","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"i have received semi defrost. why it is semi ? i ordered fully defrost. And no where it mentioned semi defrost on product details. what the hell amazo","answer":"You need to contact Amazon customer support","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"We did not recd base stand","answer":"Contact customer care","votes":"0","username":"NAnu","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"2022 star reating?","answer":"3","votes":"0","username":"Padmanaban R","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"year of manufacture ?","answer":"2021 you can purchase blindly awesome product","votes":"0","username":"Anand","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Who will provide warrenty for this product? Is that amazon send a warrenty card?","answer":"No one sends warranty, we can take advantage of warranty from the bill.","votes":"0","username":"Gopal Ram","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many design s in red colour","answer":"2","votes":"0","username":"Mandar Patil","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need a 165 ltr refrigerator. Can you show me one of good brand?","answer":"Go for LG","votes":"0","username":"Anand","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is required Inverter or without inverter?","answer":"Work on both with or without inverter.","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH PANDEY","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get single door refrigiratoroor with back side closed","answer":"Not completely closed posible.","votes":"0","username":"shantanu kumar das","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product require the any stabilizer required","answer":"stabilizer not required for this product inbuilt stabilizer disined by LG,","votes":"0","username":"N priyanivas","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many years warranty or guarantee","answer":"One year and 10 year on compresure.","votes":"0","username":"RAMESH PANDEY","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is Door cooling or no","answer":"No it's not the door cooling one.","votes":"0","username":"Anand Arjunaha","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a convertible fridge ?","answer":"There is a model that's convertible, choose the right one before purchasing","votes":"0","username":"Mani","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it convertable ?","answer":"In this you will get 2 option convertible and non convertible.this is non convertable","votes":"0","username":"NIRAJ KUMAR","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to get rid of my current old non working fridge? will exchange offer work that way?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Pandurang Thatkar","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"My current fridge is not working so can it be used on the exchange program?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pandurang Thatkar","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have a old non working fridge. How to get rid of it? Can I choose exchange program for this?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Pandurang Thatkar","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Where is the qr code to link the device with Lg thinq app","answer":"It doesnt have","votes":"0","username":"Pandurang Thatkar","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much weight of this product","answer":"50 kg","votes":"0","username":"Tanuj Acharya","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to know what is the difference between LG 3star 260 ltr. convertible & no convertible refrigerator ? Which is the best ?","answer":"Convertible means you can use freezer as normal refrigerator whenever you want. You can't do that with non-convertible.","votes":"0","username":"Tanuj Acharya","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a door lock?","answer":"Yes , a single lock which locks the freezer and fridge","votes":"0","username":"Customer","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kinta Vata takes power current","answer":"Works without stabilizer 100V to 310V","votes":"0","username":"Rupoo","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"You give the bill?","answer":"Yes...I got a bill","votes":"0","username":"Rupoo","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we exchange old","answer":"Yes ..nyou can","votes":"0","username":"Rupoo","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whether it has auto defrost","answer":"It's a frost-free model. Hence frost doesn't form.","votes":"0","username":"Sabya","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40371cfba6a7877c14b6"},"product_asin":"B08VRCMQ76","QAs":[{"question":"Can the refrigerator run in inverter when there is no electricity?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Shubham Tiwari","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fruit box missing at delivery?","answer":"No is there only","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj Kumar Muduli","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can t runs on a Inverter? ’","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"N M SASEENDRAN","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this refrigerator runs on home inverter?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"N M SASEENDRAN","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is having copper compressor ?","answer":"N","votes":"0","username":"AFTABEY ALAM","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"0.5 kwt?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"AFTABEY ALAM","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What to do if my refrigerator be coming heat from side","answer":"Leave it it's depends on environment temperature","votes":"0","username":"Neeraj Kumar Muduli","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Return or exchange is available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"AFTABEY ALAM","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Haw this delivery","answer":"Delivery good..","votes":"0","username":"Sivakrishna","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"We order refrigerator in month of oct 2021.Nd there is issue in refrigerator so with whom i shld contact?","answer":"Still now no issues, good product hair","votes":"0","username":"Sivakrishna","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"I am living on 3rd floor, will delivery guys deliver product inside my room?","answer":"I don't know, but side ground floor..","votes":"0","username":"Sivakrishna","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40381cfba6a7877c14bf"},"product_asin":"B091TZLL6D","QAs":[{"question":"What is magic convertible? can freezer be used for normal use?","answer":"Yes. You can control the temperature","votes":"0","username":"Raghu","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the door? Glass or Metal?","answer":"Metal","votes":"0","username":"Robert","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is freezer convert into freeze?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Robert","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is have the alarm?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Robert","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"I bought this fridge but no lights available at freezer","answer":"Only light in freeze area not in freezer","votes":"0","username":"Nilesh Patil","date":"2022-04-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is front body is glass or plastic or any other metals?","answer":"Metal","votes":"0","username":"Robert","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the door meterial","answer":"Metal outside and pvc inside","votes":"0","username":"Robert","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the shelves and door shelves arrangement is same as shown in pictures.","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Robert","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the freezer comes wiyh light inside","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Raghu","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it auto defrost","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Raghu","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40381cfba6a7877c14c9"},"product_asin":"B084499HPN","QAs":[{"question":"Is it light or blub in freezer?","answer":"Yes, There is a light in both the freezer & Fridge.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which 3star 256l models include fruit box and medical box and chilled tray with water?","answer":"Generally all two door refrigerator will contain fruit/vegetable box and ice cube tray. Additional spaces and racks can be utilised for medical and etc,. Thank you.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much power consumption intake  for a month","answer":"As per BEE star rating it is 180 units per annum. Thus average and approximate consumption is 15 units per month.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i give wrong information about my exchange product how instead off 260 ltrs fridge I gave it as 100 to 200 ltrs. Can Amazon refund the difference p","answer":"Please read terms and conditions of Amazon for exchange of product.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this fridge need a voltage stabiliser?","answer":"It has inbuilt stabiliser, so no need of any external one.","votes":"0","username":"Shailesh","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Delivery time sem day in vadodara","answer":"Please call Amazon customer care.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i exchange my old fridge then will i enjoy old refregarator","answer":"Fridge & refrigerator are the same. If your old one had gone bad, then it is worth buying a new one than spendingOn repairs.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the 2021, 2 star Model have the Inverter technology or not?","answer":"It has the in error technology.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to exchange a whirlpool single door refrigerator 100 to 200 litre capacity. Don't see this capacity option while choosing exchange","answer":"There it is. Glimpse again.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"The fridge looks tilted backwords..is it normal?","answer":"You have to adjust the legs for the level.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we install it ourself or wait for the installation guy?","answer":"You can, but if you are getting the fridge with free installation then take it.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Circuit warenty ?","answer":"Please elaborate...","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Keeping additional stablizer is beneficial or not for this fridge if there are powercuts","answer":"Utilisation of stabiliser is utmost precautionary safety measure.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do this fridge require stablizer","answer":"May be....","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40391cfba6a7877c14d4"},"product_asin":"B00K4AG0DW","QAs":[{"question":"Does this has an expiry date ?","answer":"No. I don't think so.","votes":"0","username":"ADG","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this suitable for hydropic farming?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sumit Kumar","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403a1cfba6a7877c14d7"},"product_asin":"B08SC9GVVR","QAs":[{"question":"How can I claim my warranty on this product?","answer":"Submit product  invoice to samsung and ask for warranty .","votes":"0","username":"Koushik Roy","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange me lena he","answer":"A good job","votes":"0","username":"Koushik Roy","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much emi for month","answer":"12","votes":"0","username":"Koushik Roy","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"No exchange offer or what","answer":"Yes with exchange offer","votes":"0","username":"Koushik Roy","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Full details","answer":"SN 04PA4PBT300108J & Model RT28A3021S8/HL -01","votes":"0","username":"Koushik Roy","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this convertaible","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Koushik Roy","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403a1cfba6a7877c14df"},"product_asin":"B08446154L","QAs":[{"question":"कितने वाट के है?","answer":"Bohot km bijli peeta h around 90 watt","votes":"0","username":"UD Gurjar","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you please suggest stand for this model","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"makthyar","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"स्टेप्लाइजर लगाना पडेगा या नहीनही","answer":"Jarurat nahi hai","votes":"0","username":"yogesh","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Power of watt","answer":"This refrigerator consumes 131 unit/year","votes":"0","username":"brijesh kanani","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is GST invoice available?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"brijesh kanani","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Bijali ki khapat 24 ghante me kitani unit he","answer":"131 unit/year","votes":"0","username":"brijesh kanani","date":"2022-07-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403b1cfba6a7877c14e3"},"product_asin":"B0834624G1","QAs":[{"question":"Is there any door lock in it","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Subhashree P.","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Freezer off kar sakte hai?","answer":"Yes we could turn off the freezer and use it as a conventional refrigerator","votes":"0","username":"samy8510","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we provide power input through 5A socket?","answer":"No. It's better to use 15 A socket for powering this device.","votes":"0","username":"Shubham sanyal","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a ice cube tray inside and does it have a light in the fridge","answer":"Yes it have an ice tray also light available on fridge section not on the fridger section.","votes":"0","username":"Subhashree P.","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Since it is 2020 model, from when will the warranty apply? Date of purchase or date of manufacture?","answer":"From the date of purchase.","votes":"0","username":"Samarth","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is copper binding or silver","answer":"Probably copper","votes":"0","username":"Shubham sanyal","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this fridge available in black colour?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Samarth","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use this refrigerator 24/7 or 365 days without unplugging??","answer":"Certainly,you can use it.","votes":"0","username":"Rajeev ambady","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"lamp is their in freezer","answer":"No lamp in freezer.","votes":"0","username":"sumit","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there child loch?","answer":"Very nice 👌👌","votes":"0","username":"Rajnikant m sheladiya","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have wheather sense technology","answer":"Very good","votes":"0","username":"Rajnikant m sheladiya","date":"2022-04-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get Extended warranty on the fridge, after 2 months of installtion and usage. Does Amazon have such providers who can do post installation?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Samarth","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing year","answer":"But if company upgrade by adding this lock facility that could be a very good feature in this refrigerator.","votes":"0","username":"Mohammed F.","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403b1cfba6a7877c14ee"},"product_asin":"B08SBN4PG4","QAs":[{"question":"Door alarm","answer":"very nice fridge","votes":"0","username":"SAPNA DEVI","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this refrigerator require a stabilizer","answer":"Dear Customer,This Refrigerator model comes with Stabilizer free operation (Voltage range 100V-300V). Hence separate stabilizer not required. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a clean back?","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, this refrigerator model comes with Safe Clean back. Back of this model is mostly covered having little coverage removed at bottom to allow compressor ventilation. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403d1cfba6a7877c14fe"},"product_asin":"B08345R1ZN","QAs":[{"question":"Is 2022 product available","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Asole","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Jalandhar Punjab ke liye Stock Available nahi hai pls provide the stock","answer":"select other seller","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Liebherr origon country","answer":"India","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Katte","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"What was the price of curd refrigerator grey","answer":"Around 30K","votes":"0","username":"Peeing Human","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"The door of this refrigerator is made of metal or plastic?please truly answer 🙏","answer":"Plastic","votes":"0","username":"Krishna Reddy","date":"2022-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we take gst creadit on this item ?","answer":"No you cant","votes":"0","username":"md.Aslam khan","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date2022 model","answer":"Dear Customer,This model was launched in 2019 however you will get latest 2022 model. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"During power outages, what will be the power consumption while using the UPS system/invertor power?","answer":"Never measured though but it’s quite less as our electricity runs on power backup when there’s outage. Didn’t have to pay much may be less than ₹100/- in a month","votes":"0","username":"Zaichik","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we take gst creadit on this item ?","answer":"Dear Customer,You can get GST invoice and save upto 28% on business purchases. For that you need to register for free. To know more details check partner offer section or contact Amazon India support Team. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"The door of this refrigerator is made of metal or plastic?please truly answer 🙏","answer":"Dear Customer,This refrigerator model front door comes with metal finish. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"During power outages, what will be the power consumption while using the UPS system/invertor power?","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, this refrigerator model can run on Home inverter in case of power failure. Voltage range should be 100-300V. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403d1cfba6a7877c1507"},"product_asin":"B08RZ23BT2","QAs":[{"question":"is solar panel available with fridge?","answer":"No solar pannel","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ BANSAL INSAN","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will the delivery man help to move it at 1st floor?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"MANOJ BANSAL INSAN","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403d1cfba6a7877c150a"},"product_asin":"B084ZX7XS4","QAs":[{"question":"If  take refrigerators from amazon .but invoice or bill can get phisically bill????","answer":"Surely you can get it from the seller.","votes":"0","username":"Irshad Sheikh","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"If their is problem after 2 yrs to yrs where to contact.","answer":"It is better to have the details of the same with you for all the times to come. Then contact the seller with your details and they will respond definitely.","votes":"0","username":"Irshad Sheikh","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"I alredy bought this. I want a base stand for this now. Is it possible to buy only base stand with drawyer(samsung original)?","answer":"Yes. Of course.","votes":"0","username":"Irshad Sheikh","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"how to exchange my refrigerator","answer":"See the x change offers. You may get a substitute.","votes":"0","username":"Irshad Sheikh","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403d1cfba6a7877c150f"},"product_asin":"B08SC3SN2R","QAs":[{"question":"It have chiller compartment like were we store diary product etc","answer":"Yes. It has a chiller compartment.","votes":"0","username":"Jaick A.","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this fridge locked or not","answer":"Lock is there","votes":"0","username":"Akash.B.K","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to do complaint","answer":"To customer care","votes":"0","username":"Akash.B.K","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can you deliver this product in nepal bhairhawa?","answer":"Check the Ava","votes":"0","username":"Akash.B.K","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this fridge have digital touch pad for settings","answer":"No, it has a button to set temperature....","votes":"0","username":"Prahlad Patel","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"My glass shelve is broken will it comes under warranty as have not yet completed a year","answer":"You should call Samsung customer care and ask them to replace it.","votes":"0","username":"Fatema","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the fridge available in any other colour other than silver grey","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Nilesh Changedia","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want the frize in instllment","answer":"U can purchase in installment","votes":"0","username":"Nilesh Changedia","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kotak bank cash back available?","answer":"Check offer","votes":"0","username":"Nilesh Changedia","date":"2022-07-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403d1cfba6a7877c1514"},"product_asin":"B08346545V","QAs":[{"question":"Is it 2022 bee rating, manufacturing year 2022? Please reply i wanted order now","answer":"Manufacturing year is 2021","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Hegde","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is stand is availbe with fridge or I have to purchase","answer":"Stand is not available with fridge.","votes":"0","username":"Swetha Pantheeradi","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this Refrigerater worth buying in 2022 too? \r\nYour suggestion please.","answer":"Its damaged..they wont change it..dont buy from amazon..My suggestion buy from Flipkart..Thanking you","votes":"0","username":"Partha","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i get 2022 manufactured product or 2020 manufactured product?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Partha","date":"2022-06-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i get 2022 manufactured product or 2020 manufactured product?","answer":"I have received 2022 model","votes":"0","username":"Jasbir s.","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the fridge have any Control to increase or decrease cooling? At what temp. can food last a week without getting spoilt?","answer":"Yes appsolutly","votes":"0","username":"ashutosh malhotra","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"For the Model Year : 2020, do we still get 2022 manufactured product or the 2020 year manufacturing. Can someone please clarify?","answer":"Yes we get 2022 manufactured refridgerator","votes":"0","username":"Nafees Hussain","date":"2022-06-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the color?","answer":"Its grey color","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Hegde","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i turn off the freezer completely?","answer":"No. Either you can convert it to fridge or use it as is.","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Hegde","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which size of stand will fit in this model? 65x65 or 65x55","answer":"Stand not required","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Das…","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"In freezer fan blowing sound is coming. like cpu is it normal ?","answer":"Little bit and very loud","votes":"0","username":"ashutosh malhotra","date":"2022-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we turn on the fridge before installation and keep the items in it?","answer":"Wait for LG service executive. They will install it. Don't try in unpack yourself, if anything goes wrong LG will not be responsible for it","votes":"0","username":"Nishil.SB","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this product need surge protector for voltage fluctuations?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Nishil.SB","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will you deliver to 4th floor in apartments?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SHAIKH FAKHRUDDIN AHMED","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can I get different colors?","answer":"NA now","votes":"0","username":"SHAIKH FAKHRUDDIN AHMED","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"whether curd maker is detouchable","answer":"No curd maker ini it","votes":"0","username":"Nishil.SB","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"will I get the product that is manufactured in 2022 or 2020?","answer":"2020","votes":"0","username":"SHAIKH FAKHRUDDIN AHMED","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do you deliver in manipur?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SHAIKH FAKHRUDDIN AHMED","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it releases greenhouse gas ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"SHAIKH FAKHRUDDIN AHMED","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rated power wattage","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"K M MATHEW","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Exchange offer is available..??   My pin code is 734006","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SHAIKH FAKHRUDDIN AHMED","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"looking for 253 3 star with base drawer","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"chinmay","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which other colour/s is available?","answer":"NA","votes":"0","username":"SHAIKH FAKHRUDDIN AHMED","date":"2022-05-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date 2022 or 2021 202p","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"chinmay","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's body shock proof or current shock come in body","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"chinmay","date":"2022-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the door orientation be changed to open it from right to left?","answer":"No.","votes":"0","username":"Shubham Srivastava","date":"2022-07-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the door orientation be changed to open it from right to left?","answer":"Nope","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Hegde","date":"2022-07-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any warrrnty for vegitable box","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Yuvraj","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the benefit of Inverter technology in this Fridge?","answer":"You can run it on inverter","votes":"0","username":"Yuvraj","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have onion potato box at bottom ( under legs)??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mohan Das…","date":"2022-08-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403e1cfba6a7877c152b"},"product_asin":"B08RZ2JKK5","QAs":[{"question":"Which type of plug pin supported?? Square or circle types?","answer":"32 amp","votes":"0","username":"Aniket Sharma","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is door lock available?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Raghu","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Renewed fridge order kiya hai to kharab to nahi honga?","answer":"It's always better to but new one","votes":"0","username":"FYM","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this  comes with touch panel?","answer":"No. It doesn't come with a touch panel.","votes":"0","username":"Sudha Sridaran…","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fridge back side is packed ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sudha Sridaran…","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Are EMI option available","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Sudha Sridaran…","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403f1cfba6a7877c1531"},"product_asin":"B08445QGNJ","QAs":[{"question":"Defrostatiom required?","answer":"Yes, it's needed.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any difficulty in opening the door?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"JAGADISH DABHI","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a digital controller outside..??","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"JAGADISH DABHI","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can any technishin visit this product before use ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"JAGADISH DABHI","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to buy this product there is no option to buy","answer":"I buy it Rs.15461 but when I show total price includes bank charge it is Rs.18998.very costly.","votes":"0","username":"JAGADISH DABHI","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ata to kono dalevhari charge nai to,","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"JAGADISH DABHI","date":"2022-04-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 2022 model?","answer":"Good production","votes":"0","username":"M.ponraj","date":"2022-07-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf403f1cfba6a7877c1538"},"product_asin":"B08SC2ZTDP","QAs":[{"question":"Is the freezer shutter acrylic or plastic?","answer":"Plastic","votes":"0","username":"Pritesh Dalvi","date":"2022-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there only 2 legs 🦵 for this model ha ? I got only 2 legs in front side","answer":"Yes,There is only two leg, but there is support system at back","votes":"0","username":"Belal Tabish","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Model year","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the freezer have light ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Peehu","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"My house is in distance of 100 mtr from. Do delivery boy deliver in 176063?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Peehu","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does ice form near freezing box","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Peehu","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"My house is on Third floor do delivery boy delivers at my door","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Peehu","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"My house is on Third floor!.  do delivery boy delivers at my door?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Peehu","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Delivar at pimparkhed is possible?","answer":"Yed","votes":"0","username":"Peehu","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dimension provided by Amazon is incorrect","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Peehu","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"After switching on fridge post unboxing 2 sides are heating up ...is it normal or is it issue with device","answer":"Think you need to call customer care if it's too hot. But placing it in a place where there's enough Breeze helps","votes":"0","username":"PATIENCE INDEED.","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this need stabilizer if there is power fluctuations in home","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Peehu","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"The fridge is missing one leg and is therefore unstable. It is working fine. How can this be fixed?","answer":"Yes it will take 2 hours max","votes":"0","username":"PSSINGH001","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How do remove the deforst water tray?","answer":"Don't need to remove manual it automatically move in waste bucket","votes":"0","username":"PSSINGH001","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the fridge auto defrost","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"PSSINGH001","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many first amount for emi","answer":"Full Cash no EMI","votes":"0","username":"PSSINGH001","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many incial amount","answer":"Full","votes":"0","username":"PSSINGH001","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need to defrost and what's the duration","answer":"Yes, it will take max 2 hours","votes":"0","username":"PSSINGH001","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kiet Mein yah Kaise milega","answer":"11700. In offer","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"stater rely","answer":"3","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Frizz compration holder","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this frost free","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sundar Natarajan","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Automatic dfrost","answer":"No it's have an button","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i get both exchange and credit card purchases offer","answer":"Ylyes","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will Amazon arrange the installation for new refrigerator","answer":"Yes delivery boy open the box","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it 2022 model or still selling 2020 model as per photo?","answer":"It's is a bujet range fridge as u can buy it  low cost. 11,700","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"My house is on First floor do delivery boy delivers at my door?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there free door step delivery for this?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"How does ice take to fridge","answer":"1try only","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Plz Suggest stand for this refrigerator?","answer":"Yes add a vegitable drawer","votes":"0","username":"Sourav","date":"2022-04-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Yestu varshagaala gyaranti","answer":"Dear Customer,You will get 1 year warranty on product and 10 years warranty on compressor from Samsung India with this Refrigerator model. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many ice trays comes with the fridge?","answer":"1","votes":"0","username":"Shoneit","date":"2022-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"How does it work with solar panel. can i run it on dc?","answer":"I am not using solar panel because it’s do’s not come with solar panel","votes":"0","username":"Mohammed khuddus","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i get delivery as soon as","answer":"On time","votes":"0","username":"Mohammed khuddus","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product heating issue","answer":"I am not aware of any heating issue, but stay clear from this fridge","votes":"0","username":"Raymond Pereira","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"How does it work with solar panel. can i run it on dc?","answer":"Don't buy this fridge, otherwise you will repent. I had bought a new one, within one year the condenser coil was damaged and immediately compressor was damaged. Though they have promised to replace the defective parts, why buy such an fridge. Buy LG or Whirlpool. As regards your question, I cannot answer because I will not buy this fridge.see less","votes":"0","username":"Raymond Pereira","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40401cfba6a7877c1544"},"product_asin":"B08346HPXM","QAs":[{"question":"What’s the size of the shelves?","answer":"Shelves size is enough but vegetable basket is very small. Since Samsung compressor is inside the body so more space is taken by compressor and basket from behind is curved and very less in size.","votes":"0","username":"SK","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufactured year?","answer":"2020","votes":"0","username":"Amrik S.","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Compressor material?","answer":"All compressors are made from Steel!","votes":"0","username":"K NANDAKUMAR","date":"2022-05-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we adjust height up to 2 cm","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amrik S.","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can u able to deliver to Raagini to jamshedpur","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sanjay Kumar","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Compresser warrenty of this product?","answer":"It is all in the warranty booklet","votes":"0","username":"Amrik S.","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40401cfba6a7877c154b"},"product_asin":"B08SM5GCD8","QAs":[{"question":"Everytime as soon as door is closed , fridge makes a musical sound.Is it normal??","answer":"No ... That's not normal.. something an issue. pls check ..","votes":"0","username":"Saravanan","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is touch panel durable for long time use??","answer":"Yes this is so good. when i brought always in eco mode.","votes":"0","username":"Amit kumar Mourya","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is digital panel durable for long run","answer":"it's been 2 months and till now its working perfectly","votes":"0","username":"DHARMENDRA PAL SINGH","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pls cheak book my freej","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Also, I don't see the nozzle on the water tray to remove the defrost water. Can I get the water tray replaced with a nozzle?","answer":"Definitely there is a nozzle for the defrost water it maybe blocked or else the nozzle hole is not properly cut while manufacturing.","votes":"0","username":"FRANKABHI","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have to manually defrost this refriegerator wvery two days otherwise water overflows onto the floor. Is this normal?","answer":"We don't need to defrost in every two days, just set the temperatureas per the requirements or else just set it to ECO mode. And yes if you defrost then there will be overflow of water from the container installed behind the fridge.","votes":"0","username":"FRANKABHI","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many down payment","answer":"Some banks take down payment and some don't so you can find out at the time of checkouts.","votes":"0","username":"FRANKABHI","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much unit consumed in one day ?","answer":"This depends on your usage, if you regularly open the door, then to maintain the temperature inside the fridge compressor will be ON for longer period of time and so it consumes electricity.","votes":"0","username":"FRANKABHI","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the height of freezer","answer":"Around 20-25cm","votes":"0","username":"Rajkumar","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it  2021 model or 2022 model  ?","answer":"8 Inch","votes":"0","username":"Saravanan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Aap se nivedan hai ki mera fridge tuta hua na bhejo","answer":"7 inch","votes":"0","username":"Saravanan","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is It only runs on solar energy???","answer":"Yes it is very much power efficient and it can run on solar powered inverter.","votes":"0","username":"FRANKABHI","date":"2022-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this refrigerator comes with lock and key?","answer":"Don't buy it has a manufacturing defects....better avoid Samsung","votes":"0","username":"Venky Rao","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"On ads it 16k in reality it 20k! Why?","answer":"Yes why not","votes":"0","username":"Venky Rao","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"When this item will be back in stock for pin code 711110 howrah kolkata.....need uryent reply pls","answer":"Worst product","votes":"0","username":"Venky Rao","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"how can i buy the blue one it is out of stock when will new stock arrive","answer":"Wrost product","votes":"0","username":"Venky Rao","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this refrigerator comes with lock and key?","answer":"yes...you can see it on the left side middle of the door...","votes":"0","username":"Ashok","date":"2022-08-05 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40401cfba6a7877c1554"},"product_asin":"B08SC26TC4","QAs":[{"question":"It has inbuilt stabilizer?","answer":"yes.","votes":"0","username":"Pankaj baroi","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use witj domestic line or should it be only power line","answer":"Also used in 5A power board,","votes":"0","username":"Salman","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to claim warranty?","answer":"Warranty active as per bill date.Whenever you got any kind of disturbance in refiregrater.Call to customer care in valid dated period and booked your complaint against problem.Service man comes to your home resolve your concern.see less","votes":"0","username":"Salman","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya RBL credit card se purchase kar sakte hai","answer":"Great thing to buy","votes":"0","username":"yash","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have auto defrost?","answer":"No, it is not","votes":"0","username":"Salman","date":"2022-04-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Most of the reviewers said it has water leakage problem ,is it true? I want the answer from samsung india please","answer":"No water leakage found.","votes":"0","username":"Lakshmi","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to see storage plate","answer":"Not good","votes":"0","username":"DHILLIPKUMAR .R","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40411cfba6a7877c155b"},"product_asin":"B08445PP98","QAs":[{"question":"Is there ice trays with this model ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"yogesh","date":"2022-06-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"I am facing issue with door that is not getting closed it seems that it is not properly adjusted","answer":"Dear Customer,We apologize for the inconvenience caused. Please check if anything stuck in the shelf which is not allowing to close the door properly. In case you are still facing issues please book a service appointment for nearest Samsung service center through Samsung India support webpage or call our support team on toll free number 1800-40-7267864  and whats app 1800-5-7267864. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product need stabilizer?","answer":"Dear Customer,This Refrigerator model comes with Stabilizer free operations. Protect the refrigerator from power fluctuations. The Stabilizer Free Operation keeps it working steadily and reliably. If the voltage increases too much it automatically cuts the power to prevent electrical damage. Stabilizer free operation range is (100V - 300V). Hence separate stabilizer not required. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be the manufacturing year?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Vyshakh","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is dimensions of this freezer?","answer":"Dear Customer,This Refrigerator model net dimensions (WxHxD) cm is  578.1 x 1325.2 x 715.8. Net freezer capacity of this model is 18 L. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many watts consumption","answer":"Dear Customer,Annual electricity consumption of this model is 104 Units.  Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many time take to make ice","answer":"Dear Customer,The time taken to make Ice in freezer depends on the temperature level you have set, amount of foods items kept in refrigerator and number of times freezer door opens. Usually it takes 6-12 Hrs to make Ice. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Hw to defrost pls..?","answer":"Dear Customer,Manual defrosting is done with help of button available inside fridge section. In case you are still facing issue to manually defrost refrigerator please check e-manual available in Samsung India support webpage or contact our toll free number 1800-40-7267864  and whats app 1800-5-7267864. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a defrost button inside ?","answer":"Dear Customer,Yes, the defrosting button is available inside the fridge section along with the temperature controller. For more details, you can refer e-manual available in the Samsung India support webpage or contact our toll free number 1800-40-7267864  and whats app 1800-5-7267864. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do i need stablizee for voltaze fluctuation to use such refrigerator?","answer":"घर में मेरे 3 किलोवॉट का स्टेबलाइजर लगा है । मैं ये फ्रिज प्रयोग करता हूं मुझे कोई दिक्कत नहीं होती । सबसे अच्छा है आप पूरे घर के लिए एक स्टेबलाइजर लगवा लो अपनी जरूरत के अनुसार 3 किलो या 5 किलोवॉट का । जिससे सारी समस्या खत्म","votes":"0","username":"Ubaidullah A.","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Back side image not showing","answer":"Dear Customer,This Refrigerator model comes with covered Safe Clean back. To check back image please refer Samsung India Official webpage. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-05-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it manufacturing year 2022  ?","answer":"Yes manufacturing date is 2022","votes":"0","username":"Ashok Sunkar","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"My old refrigerator is not working and i want to exchange","answer":"Not","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek Tyagi","date":"2022-07-18 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40421cfba6a7877c157c"},"product_asin":"B08346JDBY","QAs":[{"question":"Is this refregerator having stabilizer? Or it is working without stabilizer?","answer":"No need of stabilizer","votes":"0","username":"Kotivada Satish","date":"2022-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is refrigerator is 2pin connector?","answer":"It is three pin connector.","votes":"0","username":"S P Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have wire mesh visible st back side?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"S P Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will any service engineer come for installation?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"S P Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wich glasss selves with us?","answer":"Thoughnd glass","votes":"0","username":"Govind","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"The freezer is open from the top side(Metal is not fully closed) is it expected?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Govind","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"At the time of delivery,  the key is damaged. Can i buy yhe key separately??","answer":"Na","votes":"0","username":"Govind","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i buy yhe key?","answer":"May be","votes":"0","username":"Govind","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"If somethong is damaged or i need service, how can i get it? can i book appoinment online with a service person?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Govind","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it cDoes it comes with onion stand?comes with onion stand?","answer":"Na","votes":"0","username":"Govind","date":"2022-05-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fridge door has lock???","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"S P Chakraborty","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do we need extra stabilizer or it has in it","answer":"Stabilizer not needed.","votes":"0","username":"Diganta Das","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fridge is not balanced there is some issue in its foot rest","answer":"Adjust the lower knob.","votes":"0","username":"Diganta Das","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be delivered to 3rd floor?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Diganta Das","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Show the back side,is it open or covered ??","answer":"Coveted","votes":"0","username":"Diganta Das","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a convertable ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Diganta Das","date":"2022-04-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"I just got my fridge delivered. Will any technician come to fill gas and start?","answer":"No, you can just plug in and start.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40421cfba6a7877c1587"},"product_asin":"B08346C9R3","QAs":[{"question":"This fridge gets loads of frost in and all around freezer compartment. Anybody got this issue? How often do you defrost?","answer":"Yes, this happens bcos there isn't any other cooling vents or something in this model. Cooling comes from freezer only. So you need to defrost it every 5-7 days. I am also getting the same issue. (The above resolution is given by samsung team)","votes":"0","username":"Perminder Singh","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Installation charges","answer":"Dear Customer,This model comes ready to use & does not require installation however you can contact our support team on toll free number 1800-40-7267864  and whats app 1800-5-7267864 to book demo of product from Service engineer. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much installation charges?","answer":"Installation does not require... Ready to use machine.","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please tell me which Product model year comes, if i am buying this now in 2022 april?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Curd maker in it","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Raghavendra pratap singh","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can the door be reversed","answer":"nope","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why this product not showing deliver on pin code 845438","answer":"may not have delivery partner over their...or your location might be remote location","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there exchange offer","answer":"nope","votes":"0","username":"Rahul","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Curd maker in it","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. This model RR24T285YCR/NL is not available with Curd Maestro feature.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much installation charges?","answer":"Dear Customer,This product comes ready to use & does not require installation. However you can book a demo request by calling our support team on toll-free number 1800-40-7267864  and whats app 1800-5-7267864 without extra charges.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the rubber gasket seal on the door of the refrigerator is removeable for cleaning and can be reattached after cleaning easily?","answer":"Dear Customer,The Anti bacterial gasket is removable. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40431cfba6a7877c1590"},"product_asin":"B08SBFB2CH","QAs":[{"question":"Is it available 336 ltr 3 star rating ? I want parchase","answer":"Dear Customer,You can opt for Frost Free Refrigerator model RT37A4633S8/HL. It comes in 336 L capacity and 3 Star energy rating and Curd Maestro feature. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is curd container plastic is food grade plastic?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"RG","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much curd it can make in one go??","answer":"Dear Customer,Curd Maestro comes in 1 L capacity. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40431cfba6a7877c159e"},"product_asin":"B08345R1ZW","QAs":[{"question":"Made in","answer":"India","votes":"0","username":"RG","date":"2022-05-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does rt34a4533bx this model have door alarm ?","answer":"Timer alarm.","votes":"0","username":"RG","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whats the year of manufacturing ?","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"Xavier","date":"2022-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"How door alarm function of Samsung 324 L refrigerator","answer":"NOT HEAR ANY ALERM SOUND","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40431cfba6a7877c15a2"},"product_asin":"B08345Q835","QAs":[{"question":"Who will provide after service","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Nandhini","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the compressor compartment at the back comes with a steel plate cover?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Nandhini","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this refridgerator has steel body ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Narender","date":"2022-05-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rt37t4513s8/hl is this model defective..? as per comment from one of the customer here it was removed from listing.","answer":"I have been using this 345 lit 3 star unit for more than a month now and am overall happy with the performance even in this peak summer.","votes":"0","username":"Nandhini","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the product same as described in photo? And has Coolpack and ice box in it?","answer":"Yes . It is.","votes":"0","username":"Atul","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"has it got lock ?","answer":"No, but it's not needed too. The door gets closed well and if it's not closed an alarm will be triggered.","votes":"0","username":"Sasi Subramaniyam","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the latest model being delivered now, is it 2022 model ?","answer":"It's 2021 model","votes":"0","username":"Sivaprasath.D","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the whole curd box removable? If I need more space can i take it out?","answer":"Dear Customer,Thank you for your query. Curd Maestro Box is non-removable and comes with 1 ltr. capacity. It comes with The Big Bottle Guard which is deeper than shelves found in conventional refrigerators. You can store big containers of milk and juice in the door, along with two rows of beverage cans and bottles. Hope this is of help.Regards,Samsung Indiasee less","votes":"0","username":"Samsung India","date":"2022-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it necessary to have someone come install refrigerator?  or can I do it myself? Samsung 345 L","answer":"It is required to wait for Company rep to install for availing warranty. Also it helps to find if there is any technical fault for him to see directly for action. This installation happened for me within 36 hrs of receipt of unit.","votes":"0","username":"Nandhini","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this directly from samsung store? can i be assured of product being original and after service?","answer":"I think, the units are delivered by Samsung distributors. It is original as it was installed by Samsung rep by going thru all ritual standard checks as prescribed by Samsung by verifying the unit no.","votes":"0","username":"Nandhini","date":"2022-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"In 324 is door alarm is available?","answer":"Yes . Open door alarm is there.","votes":"0","username":"Atul","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this fridge requires an external  voltage stabilize?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sasi Subramaniyam","date":"2022-05-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40441cfba6a7877c15ad"},"product_asin":"B083JNJZ9Y","QAs":[{"question":"Is the ice twister removable?","answer":"Yes it is .","votes":"0","username":"priya d","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya isme stabilizer ki jarurat padegi?","answer":"Nhi. Achcha voltage range hone ki wajah se zrurat nhi stabilizer ki.","votes":"0","username":"Mukul Varshney","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have Cool pad in the freezer?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"priya d","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40461cfba6a7877c15c8"},"product_asin":"B07R9NJCVZ","QAs":[{"question":"Will the fridge be comin in parts or as single piece.... I live in second floor with no lift...","answer":"This will come as a single ready product.Installation means the power on service and other facilities.You will need 4 to 6 people to bring it on second floor. It will not fit in any lift.Amazon will send two or one people to deliver it. They will not carry this.But the fridge is awesome 👍🏻see less","votes":"0","username":"sneha mondal","date":"2022-06-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we get ice from water dispenser?","answer":"Not come to ice  only come to water","votes":"0","username":"Mohammed Ayoub","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which company's compressor is used in this refrigerator?","answer":"It's a Hi-Sense brand refrigerator which is a good international brand, but I am not sure about the compressor","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Shourie","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Our flat don't have lift and we stay in 2nd floor. Let me know will there be any extra charges?","answer":"If you mention in your order clearly, then I don't think Amazon will charge anything extra. Amazon is the best in customer service","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Shourie","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this refrigerator has lock?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Shourie","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Servicing and available","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Gopi","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Need same fridge in lesser capacity?","answer":"Then you go for 411 Liters Amazon Basics. It's an excellent Product. I am using it. If you want lesser capacity with side by side Design, I think you need to pay double the amount","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Shourie","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the costumer care of this fridge good","answer":"Yes, provided by Amazon. Manufactured by Hi-Sense","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Shourie","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do i need to store items in it ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Shourie","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"who will provide service in nagpur? in how much time we will get service from service centre","answer":"Amazon Provided","votes":"0","username":"Sachin Shourie","date":"2022-04-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the best cooling temperature for fridge and freezer pls tell","answer":"5 and -18 , keep it in auto","votes":"0","username":"narayanan G.","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product is better than samsung","answer":"No it’s a bad product. Don’t get carried away by the price","votes":"0","username":"Manish Galada","date":"2022-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Stabilizer required","answer":"Don't buy. Pathetic after sales service. My refrigerator stopped working in 6 months and they didn't have the faulty part in their inventory. I had to chase them almost for 2 months for the refund","votes":"0","username":"Aparajit Sachdeva","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a service center in Visakhapatnam?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Aparajit Sachdeva","date":"2022-07-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"V guard bsdi 100 stabilizer  is inverter stabilizer is it working properly on it or not","answer":"Not required","votes":"0","username":"SURESH BABU","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Inverter fridge","answer":"Yes it's hisens inverter compressor fridge.","votes":"0","username":"ranjan","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to exchange my old refrigerator","answer":"Type pincode of your place and check in exchange is available or not.","votes":"0","username":"ranjan","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a service center in Visakhapatnam ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ranjan","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it be deliver tamilnadu?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"ranjan","date":"2022-07-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the compressor based on inverter technology","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SURESH BABU","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there a service centre in delhi?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"SURESH BABU","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40491cfba6a7877c15e6"},"product_asin":"B07R9NK33K","QAs":[{"question":"Can we power on and off with power botton on control panel?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Girish Goyal","date":"2022-04-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it require external stabilizer?because stabilizer needed for safeguard note written on sidewall of freeze","answer":"Not if u are in metro cities","votes":"0","username":"Neel shah","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much time it needs for getting the fridge serviced?","answer":"Never got it serviced working excellent","votes":"0","username":"Neel shah","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the capacity of water dispemser?","answer":"4 ltrs","votes":"0","username":"Neel shah","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a inbuild water purification system  dispenser need","answer":"No inbuilt purification","votes":"0","username":"Neel shah","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What sort of water connection  water dispenser need","answer":"U have to fill water dispenser manually","votes":"0","username":"Neel shah","date":"2022-04-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will water dispenser will give cold water","answer":"Yes it gives cold water","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf404a1cfba6a7877c15f1"},"product_asin":"B07R9NJFYF","QAs":[{"question":"Kitne start ka h","answer":"I have purchased 564L side by side door refrigerator, online from Amazon. It is working in good condition, no complaints are noticed even after 1 year lapsed.","votes":"0","username":"Ramesh Patrudu","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it has a separate it has freezing chamber..?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Toshifraza","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Has Amazon mislead me intentionally? The produvt description clearly says stabiliser free operation","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Toshifraza","date":"2022-06-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which star rating does this refrigerator have?","answer":"Awesome product","votes":"0","username":"Vinay","date":"2022-06-03 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any problem who wark","answer":"No it’s pretty good","votes":"0","username":"Viralkumar Patel","date":"2022-05-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there system of auto defrost?","answer":"It’s frost free","votes":"0","username":"619","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we operate single side at a time","answer":"No both will run at a time","votes":"0","username":"kishore","date":"2022-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Fridge length in inches .","answer":"Don't buy this refrigerator. You will face warranty issues. I claimed warranty three times and nobody comes to check . They are making fool of everybody . At last i have to call from outside to check the problem with the refrigerator. One more thing , this is not happened only with me , one of my known also faced same issue.","votes":"0","username":"Lokesh","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf404d1cfba6a7877c15fb"},"product_asin":"B09H37BN1P","QAs":[{"question":"How much diamensions of this ,570 liter model ?","answer":"L x W x H : 64.7 cm x 90.8 cm x 177.5 cm .","votes":"0","username":"Damerla Manohar Rao","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about AMC after warranty period?","answer":"First one year comes for all parts , for other 10 yrs . You can take AMC separately for one to three years , leaving first year .","votes":"0","username":"Damerla Manohar Rao","date":"2022-06-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What’s the star rating given by the company ?","answer":"There is no star rating.It consumes about 1.5 units a day.Star rating should be around 3.Unlike an AC power consumption of fridge is very low.I have been using this fridge since Aug 2021 and am very happy with its performance and utility.see less","votes":"0","username":"Online Shopper","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need refrigerator glass shelves is it available","answer":"Call the company service centre. They will be able to help","votes":"0","username":"Online Shopper","date":"2022-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there temperature display ?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Online Shopper","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the freezer convertible ?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Online Shopper","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why is it nowhere mentioned that 565L Haier side by side is a frost free model?","answer":"Inverter refrigerators are normally frost free. This one is frost free. It is written inside the compartments.","votes":"0","username":"Online Shopper","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it matt finish?","answer":"Yes. Matt.","votes":"0","username":"Online Shopper","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf404e1cfba6a7877c1604"},"product_asin":"B08LF1Z4S2","QAs":[{"question":"what's the height of the freezer(not the fridge)?","answer":"The Height of freezer is 9.5 cms or 4 inch approx.","votes":"0","username":"Varun J","date":"2022-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many bottles of 1ltr or 2ltr can we fit into this refrigerator?","answer":"One litre bottle 2.","votes":"0","username":"Antony Winner","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"how many Wattage","answer":"179 Kilowatt hours","votes":"0","username":"DITSHA SALES & AGENCIES.","date":"2022-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Let me know about is it having key or not?","answer":"No key. Lock with pressure or kick.","votes":"0","username":"Antony Winner","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many units it consumes per day?","answer":"100-250 Watts per day","votes":"0","username":"DITSHA SALES & AGENCIES.","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this metal body from roof and all faces?","answer":"Top plastic. Side some stickers like plastic coating. Avoid sunlight.","votes":"0","username":"Antony Winner","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Temprature ice banane ke liye kitna set hona chahiye","answer":"अगर बाहर का तापमान अधिक है तो 5 के लिए जाएं अन्यथा 2 और 3 भारत के लिए अच्छा है","votes":"0","username":"Antony Winner","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Cooling came horahe h","answer":"From top to bottom","votes":"0","username":"Antony Winner","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much time does it take to freeze the water?","answer":"In 5 it will take 3-4 hours to freeze 500ml of water in open tray.","votes":"0","username":"Antony Winner","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Any improvements with regard to defrosting issues or auto defrosting","answer":"There should be LED light in fridge","votes":"0","username":"Aditya Kumar","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have a freezer","answer":"Yes it does have freezer","votes":"0","username":"Aditya Kumar","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is gst rate ?","answer":"Ask customer care","votes":"0","username":"Antony Winner","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kitana amp load h","answer":"I dont know the figure but it take very less amp","votes":"0","username":"Aditya Kumar","date":"2022-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Sir iska veg tray kaha milega","answer":"कोई अलग सब्जी ट्रे नहीं","votes":"0","username":"Antony Winner","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Input Voltage","answer":"220-240v good for india.","votes":"0","username":"Antony Winner","date":"2022-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"cooling system in slow plz time....???","answer":"Personally i feel its upto the mark. Its quite on upper hand. Make sure to adjust the temperature according to the use","votes":"0","username":"Ayush Gautam","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we install this on our own and does it require a stabilizer?","answer":"Hi,  you don't need a stablizer. It's a plug and play. Though I won't recommend you to buy this item as its a direct cool. It just make ice all the time. And theres no option for auto defrost.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much time does it take to make ice at max?","answer":"It’s take a little but more time but the refrigerator is nice, cooling system is nice but there is no light system if you open or close the unit","votes":"0","username":"Krishna Kumar","date":"2022-04-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the depth inside the fridge (not freezer)?","answer":"Just avoid buying this fridge as it's a direct cool.. It will constantly make the ice and there's no defrost option.. To melt the ice you have to power off the fridge from the main for hours and think about the condition of the room where you keep the fridge afterwards.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it safe to keep the mini fridge 3ft near gas stove?","answer":"Yes you ca put 3 feet near to gas stove. But keep sufficient distance to avoid melting of outer body of refridgerator outer plastic body.","votes":"0","username":"Randhir Singh","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it in xuv cars","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"FJ","date":"2022-07-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we keep wine in this?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Penguins World","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it operate on Inverter when power cut happens?","answer":"Depend on the Inverter Capacity.","votes":"0","username":"Penguins World","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we store raw meat?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Mitali Saikia","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Door lock is available?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Mitali Saikia","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How does the defrost work? where does the defrost water get collected? does it require a separate stabiliser? power cord come with 5a plug or 15a plug","answer":"One is to off the knob to deforst. Extra stabilizer not required. You can connect  directly to the socket","votes":"0","username":"Mitali Saikia","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"How to put the ice door back?","answer":"As you put it in other fridge","votes":"0","username":"Mitali Saikia","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty on compressor warranty is 5yrs. On compressor","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Krishna Kumar","date":"2022-08-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf404f1cfba6a7877c160f"},"product_asin":"B08VRZV63K","QAs":[{"question":"Is it light or blub in freezer?","answer":"Yes, There is a light in both the freezer & Fridge.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which 3star 256l models include fruit box and medical box and chilled tray with water?","answer":"Generally all two door refrigerator will contain fruit/vegetable box and ice cube tray. Additional spaces and racks can be utilised for medical and etc,. Thank you.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much power consumption intake  for a month","answer":"As per BEE star rating it is 180 units per annum. Thus average and approximate consumption is 15 units per month.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i give wrong information about my exchange product how instead off 260 ltrs fridge I gave it as 100 to 200 ltrs. Can Amazon refund the difference p","answer":"Please read terms and conditions of Amazon for exchange of product.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this fridge need a voltage stabiliser?","answer":"It has inbuilt stabiliser, so no need of any external one.","votes":"0","username":"Shailesh","date":"2022-04-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Delivery time sem day in vadodara","answer":"Please call Amazon customer care.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i exchange my old fridge then will i enjoy old refregarator","answer":"Fridge & refrigerator are the same. If your old one had gone bad, then it is worth buying a new one than spendingOn repairs.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does the 2021, 2 star Model have the Inverter technology or not?","answer":"It has the in error technology.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to exchange a whirlpool single door refrigerator 100 to 200 litre capacity. Don't see this capacity option while choosing exchange","answer":"There it is. Glimpse again.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"The fridge looks tilted backwords..is it normal?","answer":"You have to adjust the legs for the level.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we install it ourself or wait for the installation guy?","answer":"You can, but if you are getting the fridge with free installation then take it.","votes":"0","username":"Amar S.","date":"2022-05-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Circuit warenty ?","answer":"Please elaborate...","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Keeping additional stablizer is beneficial or not for this fridge if there are powercuts","answer":"Utilisation of stabiliser is utmost precautionary safety measure.","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Do this fridge require stablizer","answer":"May be....","votes":"0","username":"C. Lingaraj.","date":"2022-07-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40511cfba6a7877c161b"},"product_asin":"B08448V646","QAs":[{"question":"What is the waight carring capacity of Door","answer":"It can carry enough according to its size,it's quite resistance","votes":"0","username":"7895780454","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warranty period में खराबी होने पर सर्विस कैसे मिलेगी?","answer":"Super","votes":"0","username":"Mohd azam","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"कोई अन्य रंग में उपलब्ध है","answer":"Super","votes":"0","username":"Mohd azam","date":"2022-04-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40531cfba6a7877c162a"},"product_asin":"B088PDZG4L","QAs":[{"question":"Does freezer has light in it as the upper portion has so that we can see in dark?","answer":"No light in the freezer section","votes":"0","username":"vishnuadithya","date":"2022-06-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62bf40541cfba6a7877c162f"},"product_asin":"B07SKJK7LK","QAs":[{"question":"Does it have freezer in  bottom or top?? It is showing bottom in the pic but says top in the description pls advise","answer":"Freezer is at the bottom and more convenient","votes":"0","username":"sambabu","date":"2022-05-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62cb1f0d1cfba6a787869381"},"product_asin":"B079QY27NK","QAs":[{"question":"I baught a new refrigerator date of 27june but aproblem create more ice gathered in ice box.what problem? june through csd but","answer":"First defrost it by pressing a button, and put the number to 1, 2,  or 3  based on weather conditions and load in fridge. It is normal don't worry.","votes":"0","username":"Kannayya","date":"2022-07-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62cf130f1cfba6a7878b41ae"},"product_asin":"B08R4YV223","QAs":[{"question":"What refrigerant is used ?","answer":"Nicely working no any problem till date 1.5 yers","votes":"0","username":"Nishant More","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Koi or bank se payment ho skti h","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Nishant More","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Down payment kitni krni hogi","answer":"Flexible","votes":"0","username":"Nishant More","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Warenty period on compressor","answer":"10 Years","votes":"0","username":"Nishant More","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Compresses Warenty","answer":"10 years","votes":"0","username":"Nishant More","date":"2022-07-13 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62dee4f91cfba6a787b50cdf"},"product_asin":"B08RZ1FLSD","QAs":[{"question":"What is warranty period ??","answer":"1 year","votes":"0","username":"I.Praveenkumar","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"62eeb6ee1cfba6a787de56f4"},"product_asin":"B078YJ5SW8","QAs":[{"question":"Label period","answer":"It doesn't have a cooling control (Regulator or proper design) for Vegetable storage (bottom) and hence it freezing vegetables even at low cool setting of the temperature knob. Also, there are 2 holes given backside of the Fresh keeper in the vegetable compartment but are closed with foam and there is no answer from Whirlpool technician.Whirlpool technician visited few times and changed the thermostat and asked us to observe few days every time he visited, but no use and there is no further resolution from Whirlpool.I am not satisfied with this product as it was not suitable to keep Vegetables fresh and my old single door fridge is much better than the new 3door Whirlpool fridge.see less","votes":"0","username":"srinivas","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why is the energy consumption of 300l proton ray model very high compared to 260l and 330l versions of the same model?","answer":"It doesn't have a cooling control or regulator or proper design for Vegetable storage (bottom) and hence it freezing vegetables even at low setting of the temperature knob. Also, there are 2 holes given backside of the Fresh keeper in the vegetable compartment but are closed with foam and there is no answer from Whirlpool technician.Whirlpool technician visited few times and changed the thermostat and asked us to observe few days every time he visited, but no use and there is no further resolution from Whirlpoolsee less","votes":"0","username":"srinivas","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What about warranty","answer":"It doesn't have a cooling control or regulator or proper design for Vegetable storage (bottom) and hence it freezing vegetables even at low setting of the temperature knob. Also, there are 2 holes given backside of the Fresh keeper in the vegetable compartment but are closed with foam and there is no answer from Whirlpool technician.Whirlpool technician visited few times and changed the thermostat and asked us to observe few days every time he visited, but no use and there is no further resolution from Whirlpoolsee less","votes":"0","username":"srinivas","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"}]}
